Today we're going to be learning how to play Portal, a game by Valve Software, a company with which I have no affiliation.
All right here we are going into test chamber 10.
You can see there are some stairs here.
The voice that's talking to me is having some glitches right now.
That's another sign that things aren't well in the world of Portal and that even in the world where things aren't what they seem, things even still, aren't what they seem.
So, here's our orange exit portal and here are the stairs.
We can't jump up there, we can't jump high enough.
We need to find a way to use the portals to get us there.
One thing we can do is make a blue portal here and look out of it.
We can see the orange portal is above us, so if we walk through we just fall down.
But maybe if we jump through the blue portal it'll carry us through and it'll launch us out of the orange one to get enough distance to go up these stairs.
Let?s see if that works.